http://www.dfcufinancial.com/privacy-policy/

Digital Wallets
Learn about your new Platinum Mastercard.
Forms
Get started with a Business Banker today.
Money Management
Get a critical overview of your finances all in one place with our Money Management tool.
Home / Privacy Policy
DFCU Financial (DFCU) is committed to protecting your privacy. We recognize the importance of protecting the personal information of our members and our obligation to keep the information secure and confidential.
When you access our website and services offered through our website, we have access to your personal information. We use a technology nicknamed “cookies.” A “cookie” is a small text file that may be created on your computer when you visit a Web site (if your computer accepts cookies). We use this information to assist in the collection of site visit statistics.
We also may store a temporary cookie on your computer to keep track of information while you complete any online forms or applications and during any internet banking sessions. Once you close your browser, we remove the temporary cookie from your computer.
As a general rule, DFCU Financial does not disclose to third parties private information you submit that personally identifies you. However, there are several exceptions to this general rule, which include, but are not limited to the following:
when it’s necessary for completing transactions,
in order to verify the existence and condition of your account for a party, such as a credit bureau or merchant,
in order to comply with a government agency or court order, or
if you give us written permission.
Please feel free to contact us if you should have any questions.
Related Pages
Security & Fraud Protection
Full Privacy Policy
Download our full Privacy Policy Disclosure in PDF format.
Back to top
Speedbump Modal Called Incorrectly!
I Understand
Cancel
